marham.pk 2019-05-03

# Terms & Conditions

Purpose of this document is to assist those who are concerned directly or indirectly about the online use of their 'Personally Identifiable Information (PPI)'. PPI can be used as such or in combination with other data for identification, location or contacting relevant person. Please read on to know our methods of using, collection, protection and overall use of PPI for our website and app.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When you register on our site we may collect information including

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Mailing Address

When do we collect information?

We collect the said information when you register on our site through web or via Marham app.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register,

  * Make a purchase
  * Sign up for our email list or newsletter
  * For a survey or marketing campaign
  * Surf the website

Use certain other site features in the following ways:

  1. To personalize your website experience and offer you content and products as per your inclinations.
  2. To amend and update our website to better serve you.
  3. To respond to customer service inquiries appropriately.
  4. To manage rating and reviews of website.
  5. To identify and register doctors on our website.
  6. To verify doctor's registrations with PMDC.

How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply may be encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

Do we use 'Cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process information.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted and licensed third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that makes your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still make appointments.

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, share or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance written notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses and purposes.

Third-party links

We do offer third party services which are labeled as such.

Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

It is advised to visit the following link:

<https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in future.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

Email SPAM

We do not spam and only collect your email address in order to:

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

Copyrights

All the content, images, graphics, text, videos (Including YouTube videos), material, structure and its arrangement is property of Marham and protected under the copy right laws. Reproducing or copying any of its part or whole of site is therefore illegal. Any person or organization found guilty will be dealt as per law. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.

Trade Marks:

Marham is a registered trademark and property of Marham.pk. The management has due rights to attain legal help against misuse, theft or any infringement.

Changes to Privacy Policy and Disclaimer:

If we happen to change our policy or disclaimer statement we will be sharing it here on the page to keep you updated of amendments.

Data Theft

All data contained by the website and application is collected by Team Marham. We own complete rights of this data and legal action would be taken if we found any instance of theft of data.

Contact Marham

If there are any ambiguities or queries regarding this privacy policy, Contact us here:

Marham.pk, Lahore, 54000 Punjab, Pakistan

info@marham.pk
